export const quizData = [
    {
        question: "1. What does HTML stand for?",
        options: ["Hyper Text Preprocessor", "Hyper Text Markup Language", "Hyper Text Multiple Language", "Hyper Text Multi Language"],
        answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language"
    },
    {
        question: "2. What does CSS stand for",
        options: ["Control Style Sheets", "Cascading Simple Sheets", "Cascading Style Sheets", "Car's SUVs S"],
        answer: "Cascading Style Sheets"
    },
    {
        question: "3. What does XML stand for?",
        options: ["eXtended Markup Language", "eXtensible Markup Language", "eXtension Math Link", "eXpensive Money Loan"],
        answer: "eXtensible Markup Language"
    },
    {
        question: "4. What does SEO stand for?",
        options: ["Search Engine Orientation", "Script Engine Orientation", "Search Engine Order", "Search Engine Optimization"],
        answer: "Search Engine Optimization"
    },
    {
        question: "5. What does API stand for",
        options: ["Application Programming Interface", "Appliances Programming Instruction", "Appliances Programming Interface", "Application Programming Instruction"],
        answer: "Application Programming Interface"
    },
    {
        question: "6. What does DOM stand for?",
        options: ["Doctype Object Model", "Document Object Model", "Document Object Module", "Docstring Object Model"],
        answer: "Document Object Model"
    },
    {
        question: "7. Which language runs in a web browser?",
        options: ["Java", "C", "Python", "JavaScript"],
        answer: "JavaScript"
    },
    {
        question: "8. Fullform of JS?",
        options: ["JavaScript", "JavaScience", "JavaS", "Javasecure"],
        answer: "JavaScript"
    },
    {
        question: "9. Who develop JS?",
        options: ["santa", "brendan Eich", "george", "Neck"],
        answer: "brendan Eich"
    },
    {
        question: "10. When JS develope?",
        options: ["1995", "1990", "1999", "1892"],
        answer: "1995"
    },   
];